[
{"question": "游游", "response": "Bolivia" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Peru" }, 
{"question": "游뷣릖", "response": "Argentina" }, 
{"question": "游뷣릖", "response": "Australia" }, 
{"question": "游쀯릖", "response": "Espa침a" }, 
{"question": "游뻟릖", "response": "Canad치" }, 
{"question": "游뾇릖", "response": "Alemania" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Portugal" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Rusia" }, 
{"question": "游뻟릖", "response": "Chile" }, 
{"question": "游섫릖", "response": "Guatemala" }, 
{"question": "游뻟릖", "response": "China" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Jap칩n" }, 
{"question": "游뾇릖", "response": "Alemania" },
{"question": "游뻟릖", "response": "Cuba" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Puerto Rico" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Brasil" }, 
{"question": "游쥟릖", "response": "Ucrania" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Panam치" }, 
{"question": "游쉻릖", "response": "Italia" }, 
{"question": "游쀯릖", "response": "Ecuador" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Venezuela" }, 
{"question": "游뻟릖", "response": "Colombia" }, 
{"question": "游쓇릖", "response": "M칠xico" }, 
{"question": "游쉻릖", "response": "India" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Paraguay" }
]
